<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daris&#39;s Newsroom</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daris&#39;s Newsroom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2019, Daris Idirene; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:52:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is the world’s fastest framework for building websites. It is written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID19 Mutation</title>
      <link>/posts/covidstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covidstory/</guid>
      <description>SARS COVID 19 Virus might have mutated A colored scanning electron micrograph of a dying cell infected with the coronavirus, with viral particles in red.
All viruses mutate, and the coronavirus is no exception. But there is no compelling evidence yet that it is evolving in a way that has made it more contagious or more deadly.
A preprint study — posted online, but not published in a scientific journal and not yet peer-reviewed — has set the internet afire by suggesting otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake UFO News</title>
      <link>/posts/ufostory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ufostory/</guid>
      <description>The US Department of Defense has released three declassified videos of &amp;ldquo;unexplained aerial phenomena&amp;rdquo;.
The Pentagon said it wanted to &amp;ldquo;clear up any misconceptions by the public on whether or not the footage that has been circulating was real&amp;rdquo;.
The videos had already been leaked in 2007 and 2017.
Two were published by the New York Times, while the third was leaked by an organisation co-founded by former Blink-182 singer Tom DeLonge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>False Breaking News Big Foot Caught</title>
      <link>/posts/newsstory01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/newsstory01/</guid>
      <description>Bigfoot caught on camera “My friend and I got permission to fly our drones at Salt Fork State Park in Ohio,” one of the men writes, in a post accompanying the video. “While we were there we heard many strange noises and we believe we may have found the Ohio Grassman/Bigfoot/Sasquatch.”
Ohio Grassman is a local nickname for Bigfoot.
Bigfoot has become better known and a phenomenon in popular culture, and sightings have spread throughout North America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>our school</title>
      <link>/posts/post01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post01/</guid>
      <description>GEMS Metropole School is a supportive and caring community. It is easily accessible to parents from nearby communities with over 100 nationalities in the school. Every teacher, Learning Support Assistant and member of the admin and premises team, act as role models in order for children to achieve the highest standards. Alongside our dedicated staff, are our community of parents and carers who come from a wide range of cultures and backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>